{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Management Information Systems",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "Information Systems",
    "LastModified": "19 February 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Elmer Felisilda"
    ],
    "References": [
      ""
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What term refers to a number, statement, etc. that represents specific data?",
      "answer": "Data",
      "choices": [
        "Information",
        "System",
        "Data",
        "Timeliness"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a collection of data?",
      "answer": "Information",
      "choices": [
        "Data",
        "Information",
        "Subsystems",
        "Completeness"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of information states that info must be up to date?",
      "answer": "Timeliness",
      "choices": [
        "Appropriateness",
        "Accuracy",
        "Conciseness",
        "Timeliness"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of information requires the system to have relevant info in every module for users who need it?",
      "answer": "Appropriateness",
      "choices": [
        "Accuracy",
        "Appropriateness",
        "Understandability",
        "Timeliness"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of information states that info must be correct or precise?",
      "answer": "Accuracy",
      "choices": [
        "Accuracy",
        "Completeness",
        "Data",
        "System boundaries"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of information states that info must only contain the minimum detail appropriate to the user?",
      "answer": "Conciseness",
      "choices": [
        "Conciseness",
        "Timeliness",
        "Appropriateness",
        "System environment"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of information states that info and its format and presentation must be understandable?",
      "answer": "Understandability",
      "choices": [
        "Understandability",
        "Accuracy",
        "System",
        "Subsystem interface"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of information states that info must be complete based on the requirements?",
      "answer": "Completeness",
      "choices": [
        "Completeness",
        "Understandability",
        "System feedback",
        "System environment"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term refers to components that are interrelated and work together with a common goal to accept inputs and outputs?",
      "answer": "System",
      "choices": [
        "System",
        "System boundaries",
        "System environment",
        "Subsystem interface"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the general term for a computer or other piece of technology and its dependencies?",
      "answer": "System in computing",
      "choices": [
        "System",
        "System in computing",
        "System environment",
        "Timeliness"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term encompasses all working parts required to run a technical process?",
      "answer": "System in computing",
      "choices": [
        "System",
        "System in computing",
        "Data",
        "Accuracy"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What defines the scope of activities in which viewing or accessing any module of a system is limited?",
      "answer": "System boundaries",
      "choices": [
        "System environment",
        "System feedback",
        "Subsystem interface",
        "System boundaries"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term describes that every user has specific access on each module of a system?",
      "answer": "System boundaries",
      "choices": [
        "Subsystems",
        "System feedback",
        "System boundaries",
        "Subsystems"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for parts of a system that have different objectives and interactions based on requirements?",
      "answer": "Subsystems",
      "choices": [
        "System boundaries",
        "System environment",
        "System feedback",
        "Subsystems"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term describes that all parts of a system use the given resources to meet the given objective?",
      "answer": "Subsystems",
      "choices": [
        "System",
        "System feedback",
        "Subsystem interface",
        "Subsystems"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What serves as the connection to display the output of one system to the input of another?",
      "answer": "Subsystem interface",
      "choices": [
        "System boundaries",
        "Subsystems",
        "System environment",
        "Subsystem interface"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term refers to people or organizations that give and receive data from the system?",
      "answer": "System environment",
      "choices": [
        "System boundaries",
        "System feedback",
        "Subsystem interface",
        "System environment"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term describes effective feedback assuring users that the system can achieve its goals?",
      "answer": "System feedback",
      "choices": [
        "System boundaries",
        "Subsystems",
        "System environment",
        "System feedback"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term describes that every system always needs feedback to be able to do its job and process accurately based on the requirements?",
      "answer": "System feedback",
      "choices": [
        "System environment",
        "System boundaries",
        "System feedback",
        "Appropriateness"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What component of a system refers to the info the user adds to the system?",
      "answer": "Input",
      "choices": [
        "Output",
        "Input",
        "Feedback",
        "Control"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What component of a system refers to the efficiency of data processing?",
      "answer": "Processing",
      "choices": [
        "Input",
        "Output",
        "Control",
        "Processing"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What component of a system enables organizations to process big data?",
      "answer": "Processing",
      "choices": [
        "Input",
        "Control",
        "Processing",
        "Output"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What component of a system refers to the info the system displays as a result?",
      "answer": "Output",
      "choices": [
        "Input",
        "Output",
        "Feedback",
        "Control"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What component of a system refers to comments and suggestions to improve the processes of a system?",
      "answer": "Feedback",
      "choices": [
        "Input",
        "Feedback",
        "Control",
        "Output"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What component of a system refers to managing the operations in every process of the system?",
      "answer": "Control",
      "choices": [
        "Input",
        "Control",
        "Feedback",
        "Output"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term refers to interrelated components that collect, output, and process data to support decision making?",
      "answer": "Information Systems",
      "choices": [
        "Information Systems in an Organization",
        "Decision Support System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Information Systems"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term refers to a system that may consist of hardware, software, people, procedures, and telecommunication?",
      "answer": "Information Systems in an Organization",
      "choices": [
        "Information Systems",
        "Decision Support System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Information Systems in an Organization"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What term involves factors such as organization structure, business procedure, culture, environment, and management decisions?",
      "answer": "Information Systems in an Organization",
      "choices": [
        "Information Systems",
        "Decision Support System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Information Systems in an Organization"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system is widely used?",
      "answer": "Transaction Processing System",
      "choices": [
        "Decision Support System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Expert Support System",
        "Transaction Processing System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system records data collected at the boundaries of organizations?",
      "answer": "Transaction Processing System",
      "choices": [
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Expert Support System",
        "Transaction Processing System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system records transactions inside an organization?",
      "answer": "Transaction Processing System",
      "choices": [
        "Decision Support System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Transaction Processing System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system includes a sequence of activities such as marketing, manufacturing, assembly, and packing?",
      "answer": "Supply Chain Management System",
      "choices": [
        "Customer Relationship Management System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Decision Support System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system manages the relationship between a customer and an organization?",
      "answer": "Customer Relationship Management System",
      "choices": [
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Expert Support System",
        "Customer Relationship Management System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system is used by service representatives to talk to their customers via phone?",
      "answer": "Customer Relationship Management System",
      "choices": [
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Expert Support System",
        "Customer Relationship Management System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system is used to compete with other organizations?",
      "answer": "Business Intelligence Systems",
      "choices": [
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Expert Support System",
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Customer Relationship Management System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system accesses massive data, usually larger databases called data warehouses?",
      "answer": "Business Intelligence Systems",
      "choices": [
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Decision Support System",
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Expert Support System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system helps to find actions and answers to questions like \"What If?\"",
      "answer": "Decision Support System",
      "choices": [
        "Decision Support System",
        "Expert Support System",
        "Supply Chain Management System",
        "Customer Relationship Management System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of information system uses AI to preserve the knowledge of an expert and to solve problems?",
      "answer": "Expert Support System",
      "choices": [
        "Expert Support System",
        "Business Intelligence Systems",
        "Transaction Processing System",
        "Customer Relationship Management System"
      ],
      "reference": "01 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    }
  ]
}